Seymour S. Cohen Papers 1938-1990 Mss.Ms.Coll.48
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1940-1990; 11.5 linear feet
  - Luria, Salvador E., 1947-1969, 1984; 24.0 Item(s) (Box 13)
    Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- National Academy of Sciences; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Publication; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Lwoff, André, 1948-1981, n.d. (Box 13)
  - Maaløe, Ole, 1959, 1966 (Box 13)
    Westengaard, Mogens
  - Maas, Werner K., 1971 (Box 13)
  - McAllister, Robert M., 1964 (Box 13)
  - McCann, Peter P., 1976-1984 (Box 13)
  - McCarthy, Kevin J., 1981-1984 (Box 13)
  - McCormack, Mary, 1980-1981 (Box 13)
  - McCormick, Donald B., 1983 (Box 13)
  - McCormick, Francis Patrick, 1975-1980 (Box 13)
  - McDermott, Walsh, 1968 (Box 13)
  - MacDonald, Russell E., 1966 (Box 13)
  - McElroy, William D., 1962-1965 (Box 13)
  - McGowan, 1984 (Box 13)
  - McGrady, Patrick M., 1962-1971 (Box 13)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1966-1967 (Box 13)
  - McIntosh, Ken, 1974 (Box 13)
  - McLaughlin, Alan, 1981 (Box 13)
  - McNair Scott, Dwight Baker, 1958-1985 (Box 13)
  - Macura, Anna B., 1979-1985 (Box 13)
  - Magasanik, Boris, 1958 (Box 13)
  - Magee, Wayne E., 1962-1974 (Box 13)
    -See also Ser.I, The Upjohn Company
  - Mager, J., 1963, 1965 (Box 13)
  - Magnusson, Ronald P., 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Mahler, Henry R., 1980 (Box 14)
  - Malbon, Craig, 1979, 1987 (Box 14)
  - Male, Carolyn, 1974 (Box 14)
  - Maley, Frank, 1977-1990, n.d. (Box 14)
    Maley, Gladys
  - Maley, Gladys (Box 14)
    -See Ser.I, Maley, Frank
  - Malmberg, Russell L., 1981 (Box 14)
  - Mankodi, B.S., 1963 (Box 14)
  - Manson, Lionel, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Mansour, Tag E., 1978 (Box 14)
  - Manteuil, Simone, 1975 (Box 14)
  - Marble, Mary Gene, 1973 (Box 14)
  - Mardovich, Herbert, 1968 (Box 14)
  - Marder, Victor J., 1982 (Box 14)
  - Margalith, Miriam, 1979-1985 (Box 14)
  - Margulis, Lynn, 1969-1973 (Box 14)
  - Marine Biological Laboratory, 1950-1972 (Box 14)
  - Markert, Clement L., 1957 (Box 14)
  - Markham, Roy, 1957-1958, 1972, 1980 (Box 14)
  - Marks, Paul A., 1973, 1975 (Box 14)
  - Marr, J. Joseph, 1978 (Box 14)
  - Marsh, Julian, 1967 (Box 14)
  - Marshak, Alfred, 1950-1951, n.d. (Box 14)
  - Marton, Laurence J., 1976-1983 (Box 14)
  - Marvin, Don, 1964 (Box 14)
  - Marx, Ken, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Mason, Howard S., 1963 (Box 14)
  - Mathews, Christopher King (Box 14)
    - Folder #1, 1961-1972 (Box 14)
    - Folder #2, 1973-1985 (Box 14)
  - Matwiyoff, N.A., 1975 (Box 14)
  - Mazia, Daniel, 1957, 1971 (Box 14)
  - Mazurov, Vladimir, 1965 (Box 14)
  - Medical Biology, 1976 (Box 14)
  - Medical College of Georgia, 1976 (Box 14)
  - Medical Opinion and Review, 1966-1968 (Box 14)
  - Medvedev, Zh. A., 1961-1969 (Box 14)
  - Meeuse, B.J.D., 1966 (Box 14)
  - Mehler, Alan H., 1986 (Box 14)
  - Melechen, Norman E., 1965 (Box 14)
  - Mendelsohn, Mortimer L., 1971, 1975 (Box 14)
  - Merck, Sharp and Dohme, 1952-1978 (Box 14)
    Wyatt, Gerard R.
  - Merigan, Thomas C., 1980-1981 (Box 14)
  - Merklejohn, Gordan, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Methods in Enzymology, 1981-1982 (Box 14)
  - Metzger, H. Peter, 1974 (Box 14)
  - Meyer, Karl, 1962 (Box 14)
  - Michaels, Rhoda, 1963 (Box 14)
  - Michelson, A.M., 1965-1989 (Box 14)
  - Miletic, Branko, 1960-1961 (Box 14)
  - Miller, Gail L., 1942, 1953-1954 (Box 14)
  - Miller, Herbert K., 1953 (Box 14)
  - Miller, Jim, 1971 (Box 14)
  - Miovic, Margaret, 1969 (Box 14)
  - Mirsky, Alfred E., 1944 (Box 14)
  - Mitchell, John L.A., 1977, 1983, 1986 (Box 14)
  - Miura, Yoshiaki, 1952 (Box 14)
  - Mizrahi, Yossi, 1981 (Box 14)
  - Molecular and Cellular Biochemistry, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Monier, Roger, 1963 (Box 14)
  - Monod, Jacques, 1953-1971 (Box 14)
    -See also Ser.I, Gros, François
  - Monroy, Alberto, 1964-1984, n.d. (Box 14)
    -See also Ser.I, Current Topics in Developmental Biology
  - Montgomery, John A., 1978-1980 (Box 14)
  - Moore, Dan H., 1965, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Moore, E. Colleen, 1966-1967 (Box 14)
  - Morehouse, Ward, 1970 (Box 14)
  - John Morgan Society, 1967 (Box 14)
  - Morris, David R., 1965-1966 (Box 14)
  - Moscona, A.A., 1964 (Box 14)
    Leung, Hazel Barner
  - Mountford, Kent (Box 14)
    -See Ser.I, Carpenter, Edward J.
  - Moyed, Harris S., 1958, 1968 (Box 14)
  - Mudd, Stuart, 1959 (Box 15)
    -See also Ser.I, Green, Maurice
  - Mueller, Gerald, 1972 (Box 15)
  - Müller, Werner E.G., 1978-1979, 1988 (Box 15)
  - Mullikin, Kent, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Nadell, Paula F., 1973 (Box 15)
  - Najjar, Victor A., 1980, 1984 (Box 15)
  - Nason, Alvin, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Nass, Margit M.K., 1964-1981 (Box 15)
  - Nathans, Daniel, 1976, 1978, 1987 (Box 15)
  - National Academy of Sciences (Box 15)
    Handler, Philip
    - Folder #1, 1962-1973 (Box 15)
    - Folder #2, 1974-1989 (Box 15)
  - National Academy of Sciences--Congratulations, 1967 (Box 15)
  - National Citizens' Commission on International Cooperation, 1965 (Box 15)
  - National Foundation for Cancer Research, 1975 (Box 15)
  - The National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, Inc., 1952-1959 (Box 15)
  - National Humanities Center, 1987 (Box 15)
  - National Institutes of Health (Box 15)
    - Folder #1, 1952-1975 (Box 15)
    - Folder #2, 1976-1983 (Box 15)
  - National Research Council, 1941-1982 (Box 15)
  - National Science Foundation, 1963-1982, n.d. (Box 16)
  - Natta, Clayton L., 1978 (Box 16)
  - Nature, 1975, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Nelson, Leonard, 1969 (Box 16)
    Tosteson, Daniel C.
  - Nelson, Thomas, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Nemer, Martin, 1960-1964, n.d. (Box 16)
  - Neuberg, Carl, 1951 (Box 16)
  - Neufeld, Elizabeth, 1984 (Box 16)
  - New England Nuclear Corporation, 1958-1964 (Box 16)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1949-1986 (Box 16)
  - The New York Blood Center, 1977 (Box 16)
  - The New York Times, 1965, 1976-1977 (Box 16)
  - Newman, Jean C., 1947 (Box 16)
  - Newmark, H.L., 1981 (Box 16)
  - Newton, Alison, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Neyman, Jerzy, 1972-1974 (Box 16)
    -See also Ser.I, Davis, Bernard D.
  - Nichol, Charles A., 1971 (Box 16)
  - Nichols, Roy F., 1966 (Box 16)
  - Nichols, Warren, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Nickell, Lou G., 1972 (Box 16)
  - Nirenberg, Marshall, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Nishimura, Susumu, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Nixon, Richard, 1972 (Box 16)
  - Nomura, Masayasu, 1961 (Box 16)
  - Nooden, Larry, 1984 (Box 16)
  - North, Thomas W. (Box 16)
    -See also Ser.I, Journal of Virology
    - Folder #1, 1975-1980 (Box 16)
    - Folder #2, 1982-1989 (Box 16)
  - Nowell, Peter C., 1971, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1947-1976; 16.0 Item(s) (Box 16)
    Carter, Charles E.; Hollaender, Alexander
    Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Cancer, chemotherapy; Conferences and symposia; Hollaender, Alexander; Lectures, public speaking; Oak Ridge National Laboratory; Radiation genetics; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Ochoa, Severo, 1956-1964 (Box 16)
  - Oeding, Volker, 1969 (Box 16)
  - Ohno, Susumu, 1988 (Box 16)
  - Oka, Takami, 1981, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Olson, John M., 1977 (Box 16)
  - Ondarza Vidaurreta, Raúl, 1963 (Box 16)
  - Oparin, Alexander Ivanovich, 1962-1963 (Box 16)
  - Oppenheim, Ariella, 1970-1975 (Box 16)
  - Ormsbee, Richard, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Orthner, Carolyn, 1972-1976 (Box 16)
  - Ortiz, Priscilla J., 1971-1973 (Box 16)
  - Oshima, Tairo, 1979-1983 (Box 16)
  - Padan, Etana, 1977 (Box 16)
  - Papanicolaou Cancer Research Institute, 1969-1984 (Box 16)
    Schultz, Julius
  - Pardee, Arthur B., 1955-1984 (Box 16)
  - Parello, Joseph, 1979-1985, n.d. (Box 16)
    -See also Ser.I, Gjerset, Ruth Anne
  - Paretsky, David, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Parks, Robert E., 1974 (Box 17)
  - The Passano Foundation, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 17)
  - Patil, Suresh S., 1971 (Box 17)
  - Pauling, Linus, 1971; 4.0 Item(s) (Box 17)
    Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Invitations; Publication
  - Pavan Langston, Deborah, 1975 (Box 17)
  - Penn, N.W., 1971, 1976 (Box 17)
  - The Pennsylvania State University, 1970-1983 (Box 17)
    Rapp, Fred
  - Perini, Fulvio, 1976-1977 (Box 17)
  - Person, Philip, 1982 (Box 17)
  - Perspectives in Virology, 1961-1962 (Box 17)
  - Pesticide Biochemistry and Physiology, 1989 (Box 17)
  - Philadelphia School District, 1958 (Box 17)
  - Philips, Frederick S., 1976 (Box 17)
  - Pigiet, Vincent P., Jr., 1978 (Box 17)
  - Pirie, N.W., 1946, 1969, 1973 (Box 17)
  - Pizer, Lewis I., 1963-1983, n.d. (Box 17)
  - Plant Physiology, 1980-1985 (Box 17)
    Sindhu, Ram K.
    -See also Ser.I, Greenberg, Michael L.
    -See also Ser.I, Sindhu, Ram K.
  - Plunkett, William K., Jr., 1969-1976 (Box 17)
    Cancer Research; Journal of Cellular Physiology
    -See also Ser.I, Cancer Research
    -See also Ser.I, Journal of Cellular Physiology
  - Pochon, François, 1971-1977 (Box 17)
  - Polglazov, Boris, 1968-1970 (Box 17)
    -See also Ser.I, Goldfarb, David
  - Pollock, Martin R., 1954, 1963-1964 (Box 17)
  - Porter, Keith R., 1976 (Box 17)
  - Pogo, A.O., 1978 (Box 17)
  - Ponchet, Michel, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Pösö, Hannu, 1984 (Box 17)
  - Potier, P., 1986 (Box 17)
  - Potter, Van R., 1957 (Box 17)
  - Prairie, Celia Esther Freda, 1962-1983 (Box 17)
  - Prelec, Toni, 1984 (Box 17)
  - Price, Carl A., 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Princeton University, 1961 (Box 17)
  - Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences, 1967-1988, n.d. (Box 17)
  - Prockop, Darwin, 1964, 1971 (Box 17)
  - Progress in Nucleic Acid Research and Molecular Biology, 1963-1977 (Box 17)
    Cohn, Waldo E.
  - Prusoff, William, 1958, 1973, n.d. (Box 17)
  - The Public Health Research Institute, 1978 (Box 17)
  - Puck, Theodore Thomas, 1958, 1970-1985, n.d. (Box 17)
    -See also Ser.I, Eleanor Roosevelt Institute for Cancer Research, Inc.
  - Putnam, Frank W., 1948-1952, 1974 (Box 17)
  - Quigley, John, 1965-1969 (Box 17)
  - Racker, Ed, 1948, 1951 (Box 17)
  - Raina, Aarne Mathias, 1964-1982 (Box 17)
  - Raisfeld, Ilene Danse, 1977, 1981-1982 (Box 17)
  - Ramakrishna, Seethala, 1974-1981 (Box 17)
  - Rapp, Fred, 1965-1984 (Box 17)
    -See also Ser.I, The Pennsylvania State University
  - Rappaport, Catherine Fowler, 1950-1951, 1954 (Box 17)
  - Rapport, Maurice M., 1983 (Box 17)
  - Raskas, Heschel J., 1975 (Box 17)
  - Ratnoff, Oscar D., 1967, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Ravdin, I.S., 1964 (Box 17)
  - Ray, Paul H., 1971 (Box 17)
  - Razzell, W.E., 1964 (Box 17)
  - Redfield, Alfred, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Reed, Lester J., 1971, 1973 (Box 18)
  - Regional Cancer Center, 1973 (Box 18)
  - Rehfuss, Mary, 1977-1983 (Box 18)
  - Reich, Edward, 1965-1980, n.d. (Box 18)
    -See also Ser.I, The Rockefeller Foundation
  - Reichard, Peter, 1973-1974 (Box 18)
  - Reid, Brian, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Reiner, John M., 1947, 1954 (Box 18)
  - Reingold, Nathan, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Reissig, Jose, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Reithel, Francis J., 1949 (Box 18)
  - Resnik, William H., 1965 (Box 18)
  - Rhoads, Jonathan E., 1970-1974 (Box 18)
  - Rhuland, Lionel, 1968 (Box 18)
  - Rich, Alexander, 1978, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Richmond, Mark H., 1980 (Box 18)
  - Rickenberg, Howard, 1973-1979 (Box 18)
  - Rimon, A., 1975, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Rinaldini, Luis M., 1964-1965 (Box 18)
  - Rittenberg, David, 1962 (Box 18)
  - Rittenberg, S.C., 1976 (Box 18)
  - Robb, Leslie A., 1967 (Box 18)
  - Roberts, Richard B., 1963, 1966 (Box 18)
  - Roberts, Walden K., 1976 (Box 18)
  - Robins, Morris J., 1987 (Box 18)
  - Robins, Roland K., 1966-1977 (Box 18)
  - Roche, Jean, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Roche Institute of Molecular Biology, 1976 (Box 18)
  - The Rockefeller Foundation, 1961 (Box 18)
  - The Rockefeller University, 1968-1969 (Box 18)
    Reich, Edward
  - Rogers, Stanfield, 1963-1967 (Box 18)
    Caspari, Ernst W.
    -See also Ser.I, Caspari, Ernst W.
  - Roizman, Bernard, 1971, 1984 (Box 18)
  - Ron, Eliora Z., 1971, 1975, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt Institute for Cancer Research, Inc., 1975-1985 (Box 18)
    Puck, Theodore T.
  - Rosenkranz, Herbert S., 1964 (Box 18)
  - Roth, Jay S., 1952-1977 (Box 18)
    Lucas-Lenard, Jean
  - Rountree, Phyllis, 1950-1952 (Box 18)
  - Rous, Peyton, 1966 (Box 18)
  - Rowe, John J., 1975-1976 (Box 18)
  - Rubenstein, Howard M., 1964 (Box 18)
  - Rubenstein, Kenneth E., 1967-1979 (Box 18)
  - Rubin, Harry, 1976 (Box 18)
  - Rudolph, Robert H., 1961-1965 (Box 18)
  - Runnström, John, 1952 (Box 18)
  - Rusch, Harold P., 1969 (Box 18)
  - Russell, Diane H., 1970-1984 (Box 18)
  - Rutgers the State University of New Jersey, 1959, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
    Szybalski, Waclaw
  - Rutman, Robert, 1956-1957 (Box 18)
  - Ryan, Francis J., 1957 (Box 18)
  - Sabbach, Karl, 1974 (Box 18)
  - Sabin, Albert B., 1948-1974 (Box 18)
  - Sable, Henry Z., 1963 (Box 18)
  - Sagan, Lynn, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Sager, Ruth, 1954-1975 (Box 18)
  - Sagik, B.P., 1978 (Box 18)
  - Saint Jude Children's Research Hospital, 1971-1976 (Box 18)
    -See also Ser.VI, same title
  - Sakai, Ted Tetsuo, 1971-1982 (Box 18)
    The Journal of Biological Chemistry
    -See also Ser.I, The Journal of Biological Chemistry
  - Salk, Jonas, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Salvatore, Francesco, 1972, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Samejima, Keijiro, 1980-1981 (Box 18)
  - Saneyoshi, Mineo, 1975-1980 (Box 18)
  - Santi, Daniel V., 1973, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Saunders, John W., Jr., 1970 (Box 18)
  - Sawnhey, Ravindar, 1979-1982 (Box 18)
  - Scandella, Carl, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Schabel, Frank M., Jr., 1968-1983 (Box 19)
  - Schachman, Howard K., 1956-1968 (Box 19)
  - Schaechter, Moselio, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Schaefer, John, [197-] (Box 19)
  - Schaeffer, Howard J., 1965 (Box 19)
  - Schaeffer, Pierre, 1956 (Box 19)
  - Schapira, Georges, 1965 (Box 19)
  - Schein, Arnold H., 1966-1978 (Box 19)
  - Scheit, Karl Heinz, 1980-1981 (Box 19)
  - Schlesinger, David, 1987 (Box 19)
  - Schlesinger, R. Walter, 1965 (Box 19)
  - Schmidt, Benno, 1971 (Box 19)
  - Schneider, John H., 1963 (Box 19)
  - Schoffstall, Allen, 1973, 1975 (Box 19)
  - Schorr, Helen, 1971, 1976 (Box 19)
  - Schuel, Herbert, 1975 (Box 19)
  - Schultz, Julius, 1965, 1975 (Box 19)
    -See also Ser.I, Papanicolaou Cancer Research Institute
  - Schulz, Georg E., 1977 (Box 19)
  - Schumaker, Verne, 1955-1957, n.d. (Box 19)
  - Schweiker, Richard S., 1966, 1971 (Box 19)
  - Schwartzman, Anatoly, 1974 (Box 19)
  - Science, 1963-1984, n.d. (Box 19)
    -See also Ser.I, Balint, Robert F.
  - Scientific American, 1956-1957 (Box 19)
  - The Scientific Research Society of America, 1962 (Box 19)
  - Scott, Hugh, 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - Scripps Clinic and Research Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 19)
  - Seegers, Walter H., 1961 (Box 19)
  - Segal, Stanton, 1966 (Box 19)
  - Seifriz, William, 1952 (Box 19)
  - Seiler, Nikolaus, 1974-1983 (Box 19)
    -See also Ser.I, International Conference on Polyamines
  - Seiter, Marybeth, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Sekiguchi, Mutsuo, 1960-1985 (Box 19)
  - Sela, Michael, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Seligson, David, 1966-1967 (Box 19)
  - Seltzer, Richard J., 1975 (Box 19)
  - Serbian Academy of Sciences and Arts, 1972-1988 (Box 19)
    Kanazir, Dusan
  - Shaeffer, Joseph R., 1975 (Box 19)
  - Shapiro, Herman S., 1963, 1968, 1979 (Box 19)
  - Sharma, Opendra Kumar, 1976-1982 (Box 19)
  - Shatkin, Aaron J., 1968 (Box 19)
  - Shaw, Elliott, 1982 (Box 19)
  - Shaw, William H., 1985 (Box 19)
  - Shemin, David, 1974, 1980-1981 (Box 19)
  - Sherr, Charles J., 1982 (Box 19)
  - Shilo, Moshe, 1969-1989 (Box 19)
  - Shugar, David, 1957, 1977 (Box 19)
  - Shugart, Cynthia, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Shulman, Lawrence N., 1987 (Box 19)
  - Sibatani, Atuhiro, 1950, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Sidwell, Robert W., 1978 (Box 19)
  - Siekevitz, Philip, 1966 (Box 19)
  - Sigma Xi, 1940 (Box 19)
  - Silagi, Selma, 1965 (Box 19)
  - Siminovitch, Louis, 1957, 1966 (Box 19)
  - Simmonds, Sofia, 1969 (Box 19)
  - Simmons, Norman S., 1955 (Box 19)
  - Simon, Eric J., 1966-1975 (Box 19)
  - Simon, Harold J., 1978-1979 (Box 19)
  - Simpson, Mel, 1987-1988 (Box 19)
  - Sindhu, Ram K., 1979-1990 (Box 19)
    -See also Ser.I, Plant Physiology
  - Singer, Maxine, 1968 (Box 19)
  - Singer, Thomas, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Sinsheimer, Robert L., 1959-1960, 1989 (Box 19)
  - Skipper, Howard E., 1967-1970 (Box 20)
    -See also Ser.I, Southern Research Institute
  - Sloan, Jan B., 1984 (Box 20)
  - Sloan-Kettering Institute, 1964-1977 (Box 20)
  - Smadel, Joseph, 1949 (Box 20)
  - Smith, Charles G., 1970, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Smith, Emil L., 1970 (Box 20)
  - Smith, Hamilton, 1983 (Box 20)
  - Smith, John D., 1953-1955 (Box 20)
  - Smith, Terence Arthur, 1981-1986 (Box 20)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1973 (Box 20)
  - Snyder, Solomon H., 1968 (Box 20)
  - Société de Chimie Biologique, 1964 (Box 20)
    Courtois, Jean Émile
  - Society of American Bacteriologists, 1951-1957 (Box 20)
  - Society of General Physiologists, 1958-1970 (Box 20)
  - Sokal, Robert R., 1982 (Box 20)
  - Sonenshine, Daniel E., 1979 (Box 20)
  - Sonka, Jirí, 1957 (Box 20)
  - Sonneborn, Tracy M., 1962-1963; 2.0 Item(s) (Box 20)
    Bacteriophage and viral genetics; Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Indiana University; Molecular genetics; Protozoan genetics; Recommendations
  - Soodak, Morris, 1966 (Box 20)
  - Soska, Jiri, 1964 (Box 20)
  - South Jersey Medical Research Foundation (Box 20)
    -See Ser.I, Institute for Medical Research
  - Southern Research Institute, 1956-1957 (Box 20)
    Skipper, Howard E.
  - Spector, Tom, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Spiegelman, Sol, 1954, 1957, 1963 (Box 20)
  - Sporn, Michael B., 1967 (Box 20)
  - Springer, Georg F., 1964 (Box 20)
  - Sprinson, David, 1970-1990 (Box 20)
  - Squires, E. James, 1980 (Box 20)
  - Srb, Adrian, 1973 (Box 20)
  - Srere, Paul A., 1990 (Box 20)
  - Srinivasan, P.R., 1978 (Box 20)
  - Stacey, K.A., 1964-1967 (Box 20)
  - Stadie, W.C., 1950 (Box 20)
  - Stadtman, Terry, 1984 (Box 20)
  - Stambaugh, Richard, 1959 (Box 20)
  - Stamler, Jeremiah, 1966 (Box 20)
  - Stanier, Germaine Bazire (Box 20)
    -See Ser.I, Stanier, Roger Y.
  - Stanier, Roger Y., 1963-1982 (Box 20)
    Stanier, Germaine Bazire
  - Stanley, Wendell M., 1944-1971 (Box 20)
  - State University of New York at Buffalo, 1966 (Box 20)
  - State University of new York at Stony Brook (Box 20)
    - Folder #1, 1976-1982 (Box 20)
    - Folder #2, 1983-1987 (Box 20)
  - Steele, Eleanor A., n.d. (Box 20)
  - Steere, Russell, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Stellar, Eliot, 1967, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Stent, Gunther S., 1955-1958 (Box 20)
  - Stephen, Edward L., 1980 (Box 20)
  - Stephenson, Sis (Box 20)
    -See Ser.I, Zamecnik, Paul C.
  - Stern, Herbert, 1957-1958 (Box 20)
  - Stern, Janet Lichtenstein, 1955-1963, n.d. (Box 20)
  - Stetten, DeWitt, Jr., 1977 (Box 20)
  - Stevens, Lewis, 1968-1969 (Box 20)
  - Steward, F.C., 1963 (Box 20)
  - Stewart, Walter W., 1987 (Box 20)
    Feder, Ned
  - Stokes, Joseph, Jr., 1952-1972 (Box 20)
  - Streibel, Ellen, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Stricker, Raphael B., 1988 (Box 20)
  - Su, Ching-Hsiang, 1971-1972 (Box 20)
  - Subak-Sharpe, John H., 1968-1977 (Box 20)
  - Sufrin, Janice R., 1988 (Box 20)
  - Suhadolnik, Robert J., 1969-1984, n.d. (Box 20)
  - Sulkin, S. Edward, 1965-1966 (Box 20)
  - Sun, Alexander S., 1979-1980 (Box 20)
  - Sussman, Maurice, 1965-1966 (Box 20)
  - Suyama, Yoshitaka, 1968 (Box 20)
  - Suzuki, Fujio, 1981 (Box 20)
  - Sweek, Robert F., 1970-1971 (Box 21)
  - Sweeney, Edward E., 1963 (Box 21)
  - Symons, R.H., 1969, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Syntex, 1958-1983 (Box 21)
    Krantz, Allen
  - Szafarz, David, 1965 (Box 21)
  - Szent-Gyorgyi, Albert, 1957-1977, n.d. (Box 21)
  - Szent-Gyorgyi, Andrew G., 1956-1975 (Box 21)
  - Szulmajster, Jekesiel, 1969-1989 (Box 21)
  - Szybalski, Waclaw, 1963 (Box 21)
    -See also Ser.I, Rutgers the State University of New Jersey
  - Taber, Harry W., 1986 (Box 21)
  - Tabor, Herbert, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Tait, George H., 1977-1979 (Box 21)
  - Takeda, Yoshifumi, 1975, 1980 (Box 21)
  - Talwar, G.P., 1954 (Box 21)
  - Tamm, Igor, 1962-1964 (Box 21)
    Horsfall, Frank L., Jr.
  - Tamura, Akira, 1989 (Box 21)
  - Tanaka, Nobuo, 1987 (Box 21)
  - Tanenbaum, Stuart W., 1962-1972 (Box 21)
  - Tang, Ralph, n.d. (Box 21)
  - Tanz, Ralph, 1971 (Box 21)
  - Tarr, H.L.A., 1963 (Box 21)
  - Tatum, Ed, 1957, 1962 (Box 21)
  - Taylor, Alton R., 1946 (Box 21)
  - Taylor, J.H., 1962 (Box 21)
  - Teichberg, Saul, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Temin, Howard, 1963 (Box 21)
  - Temple University, 1961-1970 (Box 21)
  - Ten Broeck, Carl, 1965 (Box 21)
  - Tench, Alan H., 1972 (Box 21)
  - Terry, Luther L., 1970 (Box 21)
  - Tessman, Irwin, 1963-1967 (Box 21)
  - Thaler, Robert, 1987 (Box 21)
  - Thang, M.N. ("Ming Yi"), 1976-1981 (Box 21)
  - The Third World Academy of Sciences, 1986, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Thomas, C.A., Jr., 1956 (Box 21)
  - Tissières, Alfred, 1962 (Box 21)
  - Todd, Alexander R., 1955-1965 (Box 21)
  - Toji, Lorraine H., 1966-1969 (Box 21)
  - Tono, Henrique, 1960-1974 (Box 21)
  - Topping, Norman, 1953 (Box 21)
  - Torget, Robert William, 1972-1979 (Box 21)
  - Torrey, John G., 1985 (Box 21)
  - Torriani, Annamaria, 1976-1981 (Box 21)
  - Tosteson, Daniel C., 1968-1969 (Box 21)
    -See also Ser.I, Nelson, Leonard
  - Touster, Oscar, 1951-1952, 1954 (Box 21)
  - Trachtenberg, Don, 1957 (Box 21)
  - Trager, William (Box 21)
    -See Ser.I, Bitonti, Alan J.
  - Traub, Abraham, 1963-1973 (Box 21)
  - Troan, John, 1965 (Box 21)
  - Ts'o, Paul O.P., 1971-1973 (Box 21)
  - Tsou, Kwan Chung, 1966, 1972 (Box 21)
  - Tsuboi, Masamichi, 1973-1984 (Box 21)
  - Tulasne, Robert, 1950 (Box 21)
  - Tyms, A.S., 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Ubell, Earl, 1971, n.d. (Box 21)
  - Umezawa, Hamao, 1973-1986 (Box 21)
  - Unidentified, 1951-1990, n.d. (Box 21)
  - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1957, 1964 (Box 21)
  - United States. Congress. Office of Technology Assessment, n.d. (Box 21)
  - United States Department of Agriculture, 1981-1983 (Box 21)
  - United States. Food and Drug Administration, 1945 (Box 21)
  - United States. Office of Naval Research, 1947-1957 (Box 21)
  - United States. Office of Scientific Research and Development, 1942, 1944 (Box 21)
  - United States Senate. Special Committee on Aging, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Université Catholique de Louvain, 1971-1972 (Box 21)
    Some in French; Cocito, Carlo G.
  - University of Alberta, 1964-1966 (Box 21)
    -See also Ser.III, "The Molecular Biology of Viruses"
  - The University of Arizona, 1974, 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - University of California. San Francisco, 1989 (Box 21)
  - University of Colorado, 1970-1976 (Box 21)
  - University of Connecticut, 1965-1966 (Box 21)
  - The University of Dayton, 1988-1989 (Box 21)
  - University of Florida, 1969-1970 (Box 22)
  - University of Illinois, 1963 (Box 22)
  - University of Kuopio, 1981-1982 (Box 22)
  - University of Lowell, 1986-1990 (Box 22)
  - University of Maryland, 1955-1956 (Box 22)
  - University of Michigan, 1963 (Box 22)
  - University of Missouri, 1963-1964 (Box 22)
  - University of North Carolina, 1982-1984 (Box 22)
  - University of Oxford, 1964 (Box 22)
  - University of Pennsylvania (Box 22)
    - Folder #1, 1944-1965 (Box 22)
    - Folder #2, 1966-1969 (Box 22)
    - Folder #3, 1970-1978 (Box 22)
  - University of Pennsylvania. Research Club, 1969-1971 (Box 22)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1964 (Box 22)
  - The University of Sydney, 1959 (Box 22)
  - University of South Carolina, 1970 (Box 22)
  - The University of Texas, 1960-1965 (Box 22)
  - University of Virginia, 1969, 1973 (Box 22)
  - University of Wisconsin, 1973 (Box 22)
  - The Upjohn Company (Box 22)
    Magee, Wayne E.; North, Thomas W.
    - Folder #1, 1955-1965 (Box 22)
    - Folder #2, 1966-1969 (Box 22)
    - Folder #3, 1970-1984 (Box 22)
  - Upton, Arthur C., 1974 (Box 22)
  - Vallee, Bert L., 1982 (Box 23)
  - Van Camp, Betsy, 1967, 1977 (Box 23)
  - van Holde, Ken, 1989 (Box 23)
  - Van Niel, C.B., 1961, 1963 (Box 23)
  - Van Vleck, J.H., 1975 (Box 23)
  - Vargas, Carlos Armando, 1982 (Box 23)
  - Ventura, Arnoldo K., 1968 (Box 23)